(Howard:)Nine rings were made
for use in the movies.
(Howard:)Three were given to members
of the cast. The rest were destroyed.
(Howard:)Except one.
(Howard:)One was stolen.
(Howard:)Gentlemen, this is the One Ring.
(Howard:)Mine.
(Leonard:)No, it is not yours.
We all went in on the box together.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but I found it in the box.
(Sheldon:)And the laws of maritime salvage
clearly state...
(Sheldon:)...that the finder of a sunken treasure
is the owner.
(Leonard:)How is this maritime salvage?
(Sheldon:)Other than the lack of water,
how is it not?
(Raj:)Wait, Sheldon.
Stop being crazy for a second.
(Raj:)How much is something like this worth?
(Howard:)Well, it's tough to say, since it's hot.
(Howard:)On the underground market,
my guy figures--
(Raj:)-Your guy Eddie Crispo?
-Yes.
-He figures 10-, maybe 15,000.
-Okay, that's a lot of money.
(Raj:)The wise thing to do
is invest it in something practical.